beachbunnyswimwear.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy

### This Policy

Thank you for visiting www.BeachBunnySwimwear.com (the “Website”). This privacy and security policy (the “Policy”) explains the information we collect about you, how we use the information, some of the security steps taken to protect the information, and the choices you have to review, revise and/or restrict our usage of this information. This Policy is part of the Terms & Conditions of Use that govern the Website and is binding on all Website users.

If you have any objections to this Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the website.

### Your Rights

In respect of your personal information collected and held by Beach Bunny Swimwear, you have the right to:

• access the personal information we process on you

• request restriction of our use

• rectify inaccuracies in the personal information

• deny or withdraw your consent to all or some of our use of your personal information collected by us

• lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority

• deletion of your personal information from our system of records. If you would like to review, change or delete details you have supplied us with or wish to exercise any of your other rights, please contact us at (855) 212-7522

### A Safe Online Shopping Experience

Beach Bunny Swimwear is committed to providing customers with an amazing online shopping experience! An excellent online shopping experience starts with knowing your data is secure. To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. Each and every Beach Bunny Swimwear ecommerce transaction is processed by trusted ecommerce processing outfits, a 128-bit SSL connection, and PCI (Payment Card Industry) compliance standards are always observed. When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating systems. With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

All information collected to process online shopping transactions is kept confidential; Beach Bunny Swimwear does not provide, for profit or otherwise, information to outside parties except in connection with providing you ecommerce and marketing services regarding the Beach Bunny Swimwear brand. We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our terms of service.

### Consent

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place and order, arrange for a deliver or return a purchase, you imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your express consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no. You can always update your personal information or opt-out of our mailing list or other communications from us. If at any time you would like us to update your information or you opt-out, email customer service at [info@beachbunnyswimwear.com](mailto:info@beachbunnyswimwear.com). Please be sure to include your email address, full name and mailing address.

### Business Partners

Several services enjoyed by customers are provided by third-parties. Services such as email marketing and online payment processing would not be possible without the employment of established, trusted and secure systems provided by reputable companies. In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide for Beach Bunny Swimwear and you. To provide customers with the best in swimwear, Beach Bunny Swimwear tracks website traffic and use. Measurements that capture website effectiveness, product popularity, and other elements related to a customer’s online shopping experience allows Beach Bunny Swimwear to better both their product, and the Beach Bunny Swimwear online experience. Information is generic, related to the Beach Bunny Swimwear website use and product popularity; specific customer information in regards to website use is not collected.

If a customer has a concern regarding services that are provided for Beach Bunny Swimwear customers, by companies other than Beach Bunny Swimwear, please contact Customer Service by emailing [info@beachbunnyswimwear.com](mailto:info@beachbunnyswimwear.com).

### Advertising

As you browse BeachBunnySwimwear.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with BeachBunnySwimwear.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. You can visit this page (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>) to opt out of targeted advertising.

### Secure Shopping

Sensitive personal information contained in orders placed on the Website are encrypted using 128-bit secure sockets layer (SSL) technology.* In order for SSL security to work, you must use an SSL enabled browser. *Secure Socket Layer (SSL) is a technology used by vendors to ensure the security of online business. It negotiates and employs the essential functions of mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity for secure transactions.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that:

  * (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control
  * (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through the Website cannot be guaranteed
  * (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party
  * (d) WHEN YOU TRANSFER ANY INFORMATION TO US, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK.

If you still have concerns about ordering electronically, feel free to call (855) 212-7522 and place your order over the phone. Have the style number, size, and color ready for each item you wish to order.

YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE AT ALL TIMES FOR MAINTAINING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF ANY PASSWORD OR OTHER ACCESS INFORMATION.

### Note to Kids

If you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to submit any personal information to BeachBunnySwimwear.com (the “Website”). BeachBunnySwimwear.com is intended for users who are 13 years of age and older. Beach Bunny Swimwear provides high quality swimwear products to adult women and our site is designed to reflect these services. Online purchases are to be made by the card holder only, and your use of Beach Bunny Swimwear’s checkout process indicates your representation that you are in compliance with these rules.

### Policy Changes

Beach Bunny Swimwear may periodically update this Policy including for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed. Any changes made will be posted here. By visiting and continuing to use the Website you agree to accept any changes made to this Policy. Please note that this Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on the Website. Feel free to contact us with any questions about our Policy.

Or (855) 212-7522

Or contact us via postal mail:

Beach Bunny Swimwear   
3333 Michelson Drive, Suite 500   
Irvine, CA 92612
